Every time I'm out
It's not where I want to be
That's okay with me because
He's not the only one
Party girl
Lay off on the party, girl
Come and get your party, girl
I become the party girl
No one wants a party girl
Come and get a party, girl
Ricky, you want to check
the level on that mike?
And you guys, pick up the tempo
a little bit next time, okay?
- Angel.
- I'm not here.
Hey, hey, hey, where are you going?
- Out.
- I've got interviews set up for you
this afternoon and photos tonight.
Look, Lou, I told you I'd come down
and do your benefit, but that's it, okay?
Angel, it's all arranged.
You should have asked me first.
Sorry.
Angel, I'm warning you.
Don't give me a hard time.
- You'll do the interviews.
- Stop it, Lou.
You don't own me!
Where are you going?
I'm going to party until I drop.
Lou?
Lou.
I need the police.
Yeah, it's an emergency.
Miss Danello?
Margaret Danello?
The name's Angel.
May I talk to you?
Maybe later, okay?
This can't wait.
Homicide.
I'd like to ask you a few questions
about Lou Pearson.
- Ben? We just got a new client.
- Yeah?
Max Weinberg
represents her in New York,
called and asked us
to take her case.
Who is it?
Top recording star,
dozens of magazine covers,
sold-out concert tours.
Am I going to have to guess
her name?
She's waiting in my office right now.
I just-- Remember how you always say
justice is blind?
Charlene, the suspense
is overwhelming. Who is this person?
Ben, this is Angel.
Hi, Ben.
What is this place,
some kind of a museum?
I love peanuts.
No.
- Ben.
- No.
She's a very big star.
- I never heard of her.
- Oh, Dad.
- What is she, rock 'n' roll?
- Yes, and very popular.
Draws crowds of 30, 40,
50,000 people.
You're kidding.
Now, this is old.
There'll be a very big retainer.
So you want to get started?
Having Lou for a manager was sort of
like signing a pact with the devil.
Was there a romantic involvement?
No.
What time did you arrive
at his house last night?
I'm not sure.
It was after 1 2, I think.
No, wait, it was after 1 .
How is it you don't remember?
I was partying.
I went to a lot of different clubs
and I drank a little too much,
and I went to Lou's house
to patch things up, and then I crashed.
Lou was still up
when I sort of passed out.
Look, could I go now?
Perhaps you don't recognize
the gravity of your situation.
The police let me go.
For the moment.
The police might want you back.
You had a bitter argument
with Mr. Pearson yesterday.
You went to his house.
You're not sure when.
You found the body. You ran.
If I were a policeman,
that would make you a prime suspect
in this case, Miss Danello.
Please, call me Angel.
The name on the docket
will be Margaret Danello.
That's fine with me.
If I were you, I'd try real hard
to remember where I was last night.
Look, maybe I don't remember exactly
where I was or when I was there,
but I think I'd remember
if I murdered Lou, okay?
You know...
...every case we take on
requires a little different approach.
Perhaps you can jog
Miss Danello's memory.
I'll see what the police have to say.
Excuse me.
You know, he's kind of a pain.
He grows on you.
What are you doing here, Ben?
We don't have enough
to arrest your client yet.
That never stopped you before.
- Who is she?
- That's the widow over there.
They've been separated
for about five months.
- Any prints on these glasses?
- Nothing good.
Looks like Lou Pearson
knew whoever it was.
- Seemed like they were celebrating.
- Sure looks that way.
- He was stabbed, wasn't he?
- In the chest.
There's a pair of scissors
missing from this desk set.
We're looking for them.
- Mrs. Pearson?
- Yes?
I'm Ben Matlock, Margaret--
Angel's lawyer.
Well, I just told them
everything I had to say.
Well, only the good die young.
You one of Pearson's clients?
I was more than a client.
We're like brothers.
Yeah, like Cain and Abel.
Little upset, huh?
- You Detective Davis?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I just heard.
Excuse me, who are you?
Sonny Hutton.
I just flew in for the concert.
I was on my way from the airport when
I got the news. I can't believe this.
His secretary says
there's a tape of yours missing.
My tape? They stole my tape?
The new album.
Hey, if it sells like your last album,
they'll lose money.
Look, we still got work to do here.
Hey, at least you know one thing
about the killer.
If the guy took Sonny's tape,
he's got no taste.
And you can quote me as saying
that I'll be a party girl
until my party is over.
- Hey! That was a wire service!
- I don't care if it was Tom Brokaw,
- and get your feet off my desk.
- Boy, have you got a lot of nerve!
If I'm going to represent you,
you're going to have to straighten up
- and do as you're told.
- And what if I don't want to?
You'd better do as he says, miss.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Found the missing pair of scissors.
They were the murder weapon,
all right.
The lab says they have
Pearson's blood type on them.
Where'd they turn up, Rupert?
Miss Danello's hotel room.
You're under arrest for murder.
- How much was your bail, Angel?
- Two hundred thousand.
- I'm an expensive date.
- So why'd you do it?
Guys are always dropping dead
at my feet.
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
Miss Danello is innocent
of Mr. Pearson's murder.
Nonetheless, she takes the matter
very seriously.
At the moment, she is still shocked
by this tragic event
and has no comment.
Isn't he adorable?
Don't you ever do that.
I was just giving them
what they wanted.
It's part of the game. It's the show.
You keep forgetting you're not
on a stage. You're in a courtroom.
- You're on trial for murder.
- Relax.
- The press loves me.
- Ben.
Read her the headline.
''The Party's Over for Party Girl.''
They love you so much they're going
to convict you before we pick a jury.
Lighten up, okay?
We're going to set up
some rules right now.
Rule number one: you are not
to talk about this with anyone,
especially not the press.
Rule number two: the next time
we go in the courtroom,
you're going to wear
more than just your underwear.
Rule number three: the next time
you tell me to lighten up,
you're going to find yourself
without a lawyer,
without a defence,
and without a prayer. Got it?
There she is,
an angel if ever I saw one.
It is a privilege
and an honour to meet you.
I am perhaps your greatest fan.
- Tyler Hudson at your service.
- Who is this?
I am their personal
private investigator,
but most of my time
is spent investing venture capital.
But sometimes I take on
a special case that interests me.
And Angel, this is for you,
genuine Georgia pecans.
Something I might market as a gift.
Can we get down to business?
Now, the first thing we have to do
is establish where you were
the night of the murder.
What does the medical examiner
have to say?
Tyler!
Oh, yeah. That Pearson died between
2 and 3:30 in the morning.
I want you to think very hard.
Where were you between
2 and 3:30 yesterday morning?
I already told you where I was.
I was partying and I don't remember.
Look, if we can find someone who was
with you, you might be off the hook.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I was at the Hard Line at 1 1 .
No, that was Tuesday.
Okay, I know that I was
at the Dirt Club.
That was on Monday.
I'm not sure where I was.
We're going to have to retrace
your steps.
We have to know where everybody
was the night of the murder.
The widow, Janice,
Sonny Hutton, Fancy Dan.
- Danny Blaster.
- Whatever.
He was in town that night.
You're going to have to go with us.
Can l--?
All right. I'm on my way out of here.
Angel, do you ever do
endorsements?
Dad, I can't make it tonight.
I have an appointment.
You're going to leave me
alone with her?
She's not exactly dangerous.
I think you can protect yourself.
It's not what she might do to me
that concerns me.
It's the other way around.
What a pain.
She grows on you. Have fun.
You've got to be kidding.
How many more
of these places are there?
Not enough.
This is just a private party.
You're kidding.
Hey, baby.
Dan, you're looking good.
Dan, this is Ben, my lawyer.
- Yeah, we've met.
- Yeah.
Listen, you need anything,
just let me know.
Can you account for your time
the night of the murder?
Why are you asking me?
I don't know.
You said you'd like to help.
It might help. You never know.
Let's go.
Got a little bit of a temper,
doesn't he?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- Yeah.
I'll be over there.
- Hi.
- I thought you had an appointment.
- Oh, I do.
- A musician?
- No, a tax lawyer. How you doing?
Okay. I'll see you in the morning.
Early in the morning.
Early. Right.
Hi.
- I saw you yesterday at Lou Pearson's.
- Oh, yes.
I'm Ben Matlock, Angel's lawyer.
- How you doing?
- Okay.
Any luck finding
that missing tape of yours?
They looked everywhere
in the house. It's gone.
Oh, I'm surprised record bootleggers
would be that interested.
- Why is that?
- Your last album didn't do all that well.
Is that supposed to be a dig?
Oh, no. No, no, no.
I was just curious.
My daughter tells me
that Dan Blaster's really hot right now,
and I wondered
why they didn't take his tape.
Maybe they listened to it first.
When did you arrive in Atlanta,
Mr. Hutton?
I arrived Wednesday
morning, 1 0 a.m.
Georgia Air flight 1 83 from New York.
You can check the airline on that.
I think that puts me in the morning
after Lou was murdered,
to answer your question.
I guess you're right.
Clear out, clear out. Let's go.
All right. Clear out, clear out.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, cut it out. Cut it out.
I noticed you two
didn't really get along.
You want to know where
I was the night of the murder, huh?
It might help.
Why don't you ask my friends?
Ask me if you
wanna know something.
No problem.
Hey, aren't you a little old
to be out in this night air?
You're probably right.
I'll see you.
Yeah?
In court.
Ben, I've got big news.
Ron, this is Ben, my lawyer.
I gave Angel a ride out
to Lou Pearson's house that night.
- What time was that?
- Let's see...
It was about 1 :30. Yeah, I'm a DJ
and I was on the air at 2.
- I'm off tonight.
- Some other time, okay?
Some other time.
This places you at Lou Pearson's
at the time of the murder.
It's big news, all right.
You don't have an alibi.
- What?
- You don't have an alibi.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow then.
You'll see me tomorrow?
Yeah. I'm going to go dance,
and then they want me to do
a few songs.
I'm a party girl, remember?
Angel, we're leaving.
What?
Let's go.
Thanks, Tom.
Step right in here.
What is this,
some kind of rehearsal?
You know, I've had a few clients
who didn't seem to realize
the gravity of their situation.
I used to bring them in here
and sit them on a chair or a table
and I'd browbeat them into realizing
just how tough this business can be.
I don't do that anymore.
One, because it wears me out.
Two, because most people
have come to realize
that prison is a mean,
foul-smelling place
more horrible
than your worst nightmares.
I'm not sure you do.
- Unlock the door.
- I don't have the key.
But that man does.
That's true.
Matlock, don't take all day.
Matlock!
- What kept you?
- Tom had stepped away.
I hope you weren't frightened.
- I got the message.
- Good, good.
Because unless you start to look
and act like a lady,
prison's where you're liable to be
for the next 50 years.
Believe me...
...it's no party.
Yeah.
- All right.
- Baby.
Yeah.
I thought I told you
to dress like a lady.
I did.
Your secret's safe with me.
How was your evening?
- Better than yours.
- I would hope.
I found out that Danny Blaster
was having Lou Pearson audited.
And that's why he has
all the bikers around him...
...for protection.
From Lou Pearson?
Pearson was connected,
if you know what I mean.
How did you get all this information?
The tax lawyer I was with
is in the music business.
Told you I had an appointment.
I found out something else.
Dan is a champagne drinker.
So is Sonny Hutton.
Mrs. Hoffman, how long had
you been Mr. Pearson's housekeeper?
- Over two years.
- And was anyone else in the house
- at the time you discovered the body?
- No.
Did you see anyone leave the house
when you reported for work
that morning?
I saw Angel, I mean Miss Danello.
- The defendant?
- That's right. She was running away.
No further questions, Your Honour.
Your witness, Mr. Matlock.
She never liked me.
Ask her about the--
I'll take it from here, Margaret.
Mrs. Hoffman...
...was Mr. Pearson particular
about the way you kept his house?
Yes, he was.
Mrs. Hoffman, it's been stipulated
that these scissors,
People's Exhibit 6, were the weapon
that killed Mr. Pearson.
- Do you recognize them?
- Yes, I do.
They were kept
on Mr. Pearson's desk,
- were they not?
- Yes.
You cleaned the desk
the day of the murder?
- Yes, I did.
- What is that?
It appears to be rust.
But Mrs. Hoffman,
you testified that Mr. Pearson
was a meticulous man.
You let his scissors get rusty?
I did nothing of the kind.
Well, metal only rusts
when it gets wet.
You suppose someone
left them outside?
Objection. Calls for speculation
on the part of the witness.
Sustained.
Mrs. Hoffman,
Sergeant Davis has testified
that these scissors were found
in Miss Danello's hotel closet.
How do you suppose
they got rusty in her closet?
Objection.
Speculation. Relevancy?
Your Honour, I am simply
trying to demonstrate
that it is possible that these scissors
were thrown away or hidden outside
someplace where they got wet.
Then whoever killed Mr. Pearson
came back later, got them,
planted them in the defendant's room.
That would explain the rust.
Mr. Matlock, that does call
for speculation from this witness.
Objection sustained.
No further questions.
I call Janice Pearson.
Mrs. Pearson, how long
have you known the defendant?
About three years.
And in that time,
did your husband ever discuss
his personal relationship
with Miss Danello?
- Yes, he did.
- What did he tell you?
He said she had a violent temper,
she was getting some bad advice
from other people,
and he was afraid
of what she might do.
- What? She's a liar.
- Sit down.
Mr. Matlock, the bench cautions you
to control your client.
Mrs. Pearson,
were you ever present
when Miss Danello threatened
your late husband with bodily harm?
Yes, I was.
That is a lie. I never did.
Mr. Matlock, I'm warning you--
She's just trying to bury me.
Another word from you, and I'll have
you removed from the courtroom.
Your Honour, my client
is under considerable strain.
I apologize for the interruption.
It won't happen again.
I will not tolerate another outburst.
Now, please continue.
No further questions, Your Honour.
Mrs. Pearson...
...have you ever been a patient
at Atlanta General Hospital?
I think so. It was a long time ago.
I'm surprised
you don't remember better.
According to these medical records,
you were a regular customer.
In November, you checked in
with a fractured arm.
In January, cracked ribs.
In April, abrasions and bruises.
How did all these things happen?
Accidents.
Mrs. Pearson...
...isn't it true...
...that you filed assault charges
against your husband
in April of last year?
Those charges were dropped.
Answer the question.
Isn't it true you filed assault charges
against your husband?
- Yes.
- And isn't it true
you filed those assault charges
while you were being treated
for those injuries
at Atlanta General Hospital?
- Objection. Relevancy.
- Your Honour,
defence is attempting to show
that Mr. Pearson was himself
prone to violence.
Overruled. Answer the question.
Could you repeat the question?
''Isn't it true you filed those assault
charges while you were being treated
for those injuries
at Atlanta General Hospital?''
I suppose so.
Then you withdrew those charges
two days later after you were released.
That's correct.
Mrs. Pearson, are you aware
that you are the sole beneficiary
- of your husband's estate?
- Objection, Your Honour.
- Sustained.
- No more questions.
Court will adjourn until 9 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Is that it for today?
You did yourself
a lot of damage today.
That outburst could cost us
the case with this jury.
- She was lying.
- I don't care if she quoted the Bible.
That jury's looking
at a spoiled, smart aleck kid
who can't control her emotions
maybe to the point
she could commit murder.
Now, when you come
in here tomorrow,
you better act right or we might as well
just throw in the towel.
- Anything else?
- Yeah.
Buy yourself a dress that doesn't
look like you belong in a circus.
- Ben.
- Did I leave out something?
No, you covered everything.
- You all right?
- I'm fine, okay?
- Angel, I know it's been rough on you.
- Look...
...I'm sick and tired of you and
your father trying to scare me, okay?
- I know how you must feel.
- No, you don't!
You don't know anything about me!
I know your father
was an alcoholic...
...and your mother left
when you were 1 1 .
I know you spent some time
in reform school.
Yeah...
...but you weren't there
when my old man came home
and beat up my mom every night.
And you weren't there
when I got six months
for riding around in a car
that I didn't know was stolen.
Nobody was there but me.
You can't do it alone this time.
If we're going to win this case,
you've got to work with us.
You know something?
You're a lot slicker,
but you're just like him.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
How many of those pecans
did you say you bought?
Two tons.
Two tons?
I thought I had a buyer,
and at the last minute,
he backed out on me.
Oh, well.
- Say, Ben--
- No.
- Hard at work, I see.
- Hey.
- Oh, just reviewing the case.
- Have a pecan.
So where are we?
- In trouble.
- Well, the word I get
is that Janice Pearson
and Sonny Hutton have been an item
- for quite some time.
- Well, I'll tell you what,
we can take all the stuff we've got
and maybe put it in a gossip column,
but we'd never influence the jury.
We've got three people
all with a possible motive.
Janice was at a party till 4:00.
Danny Blaster
was at some club all night.
Sonny Hutton wasn't even in town
the night of the murder.
Well, we've got to break one
of their alibis, but they all check out.
Well, I have a strong feeling
this murder has something to do
with Sonny Hutton's tape.
- You know, the one that's missing?
- Yeah.
You got a clue?
No.
You're right. We're in trouble.
Well, I'm going home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
You know...
...it's too bad somebody
can't get inside Sonny's hotel room,
- take a look around.
- Yeah, it's too bad.
Sure is.
Excuse me,
could you turn my bed down?
Thank you.
Good night.
Nice view, huh?
As a rule do attorneys
break into other people's hotel rooms?
What room is this?
- Fifteen-twenty-seven.
- Fifteen--? I check into 1 427.
I guess I just made
an honest mistake.
Are you looking for something?
I'll be running along.
No, no. No, I don't think so.
Look, don't get cute.
Room service.
I didn't order room service.
You didn't order a lobster
with a side order of grits?
No.
- Mercy, mercy, me, oh, my.
- Good night.
You could've told me
you were coming here.
So could you,
but I'm glad you did, partner.
- Did you find the tape?
- No, but I did find this.
He did it, Tyler.
I just know he's our guy,
maybe this can prove it.
- Hey, Angel.
- Sorry, not now. I'm running late.
What really happened?
Come on, for your fans, Angel.
- Angel?
- Yeah?
For your fans, Angel, come on.
Did you do it?
Angel, can we possibly
get an interview with you?
You've got to be kidding.
- Where's Tyler?
- I haven't heard from him.
We'd better hear from him soon.
Nice dress.
Yeah, if you're Nancy Reagan.
Division 21 Superior Court
of Fulton County is now in session.
The Honourable
Richard Cooksey presiding.
All rise.
Mr. Matlock?
I call Daniel Blaster to the stand.
Now,
Mr. Blaster,
Mr. Pearson...
...was your manager
for eight years. Is that correct?
Yes.
Did you trust him?
Lou was a manager and a friend.
Mr. Blaster, isn't it true that you
hired an accounting firm to audit
the books of this man
you trusted like a friend?
It happens all the time
in the record business.
Mr. Blaster, isn't it true that
Mr. Pearson threatened you
if you proceeded with this audit?
Lou was just kidding around.
Is that why you hired bodyguards
two days before the audit began?
I needed extra security for my tour.
Mr. Blaster, isn't it true when you
played Los Angeles last year,
you publicly accused
Mr. Pearson of stealing from you
and you were engaged in a
fistfight in your dressing room?
Hey, I just got a little excited.
This sort of thing happens all the time.
Lou knew it didn't mean anything.
Where were you
the night of the murder?
With friends.
Would these friends
swear as to your whereabouts?
Sure.
Are these gentlemen
in the front row your friends?
Can you gentlemen
stand up please?
Would they go under the names of...
...Snake Barker,
Trashcan Reed,
Bones Lloyd, and Doctor Death?
Right.
No further questions.
- Anything from Tyler?
- Not yet.
Your witness, Mr. Park.
Mr. Blaster, are you familiar
with the property
at 321 2 Crestline Drive
in Malibu, California?
It's my beach house.
Are you in the habit
of loaning out that house
- to your friends and associates?
- Sure.
In April of last year,
did you loan out
the use of that house
to Miss Danello?
- Mr. Blaster!
- Yes.
She stayed there.
Was she alone?
No.
And who was
staying there with her?
Lou Pearson.
No further questions.
Your Honour,
with the court's permission,
I'd like to take a few minutes
to confer with my client.
The court will take
a ten-minute recess.
Why didn't you tell me
you were having an affair
with Lou Pearson when
I asked you the first time?
What happened between Lou and me
was a long time ago
and it's none of your business.
I got caught with my pants down.
I made a mistake, okay?
When am I going to get it through
your head I am trying to save your life?
Why do you really care, anyway?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I know you're scared.
Tyler's here.
How's business?
Business is great.
I understand your record sales
have fallen off lately.
A little.
The fact is you haven't
had a new album in
two years, isn't that correct?
That's not unusual.
But it is true, isn't it?
Yes, it's true.
I bet Lou Pearson
wasn't very happy about that.
Lou wasn't worried.
We just finished another album.
Yeah, that's right.
That was the tape you sent him.
- Yes.
- The one that was stolen
the night of the murder.
That's right.
Would you like to get it back?
Of course I would. It's very valuable.
It's the only mix that exists.
The only one?
That's taking quite a chance, isn't it?
There's a 24-track master
at Lou's studio.
The one that was stolen
is the only mix.
Oh, I see, I see, I see.
Did you and Lou Pearson have a fight
over what he thought of your album?
I never saw Lou.
I got into Atlanta the morning
after the murder.
That's right.
You said you flew in
- directly from New York, didn't you?
- Yes.
On Georgia Air flight...
...1 83.
That's right.
You sure you weren't in Atlanta
the night Lou Pearson was murdered?
Objection.
The witness has already answered
the question.
Sustained.
Your Honour,
at this time, I'd like
to introduce into evidence
this claim check
from a parking facility at the
Charleston, South Carolina Airport.
Recognize it?
No.
Doesn't the flight you're on,
flight 1 83,
make a stopover at Charleston?
Yeah. So what?
Mr. Hutton,
it just so happens
that a car you rented in New York
is at this very moment
parked at the Charleston Airport.
Oh, God. You know what I think?
I think you drove that car
from New York to Atlanta,
then back up to Charleston,
parked it, got on flight 1 83 to make
it appear you flew in from New York.
Objection.
- Pure speculation.
- Sustained.
Mr. Hutton,
didn't you see Lou Pearson
about your album?
I told you I didn't see Lou.
Isn't it true that he knew you were
having an affair with his wife?
No.
Isn't it true he refused
to release your album?
- No.
- Isn't it true he promised
to destroy your career,
you fought with him, and killed him?
That is a lie.
Mr. Hutton...
...if that missing tape
were found in your rental car,
wouldn't that prove
you were in Atlanta
and did see Lou Pearson
the night of the murder?
Wouldn't it, Mr. Hutton?
Would you like my associate
to play the tape for you?
Mr. Hutton...
...not 20 minutes ago,
my associate returned
from Charleston,
where he found your rental car,
had keys made, opened the trunk,
looked inside, there it was.
I repeat.
Would you like us to play it for you?
No.
In other words, Mr. Hutton,
you lied about
when you arrived in Atlanta.
You lied about seeing Lou Pearson.
You lied about the tape.
You are a liar.
And maybe something a lot worse.
No further questions, Your Honour.
We find the defendant not guilty.
Order! Order!
You play poker, Matlock?
On occasion.
Blue button.
Master dub 1 29 7 7, artist
Sonny Hutton, recorded June 1 st.
Sounds like a full house to me.
Thanks.
I owe you two.
- Anytime.
- Anywhere.
You know, for a lawyer, you're okay.
I won't argue with that.
Thank you.
Well, Tyler,
that was a very successful
trip to Charleston.
It sure was.
You know,
I met this guy at the airport
who's got a truckload
of frozen pie crusts.
I get my hands on those suckers,
I'm going into the
Christmas pecan pie business.
You know what?
I was driving through
this little town one time.
It wasn't really a town.
It was just a general store
with a gas pump out front.
And while I was
gassing up, I went in
and I saw the walls
of the general store
were just lined
with these bags of salt.
So I said to the fellow, I said,
''You must sell a lot of salt.''
He said, ''No, I don't sell much salt.
But the fellow that sells me salt,
now, he sells salt.''
www.tvsubtitles.net